An Inventory of the United States. Food Administration records XX066
Hoover Institution Archives
- Alphabetical file, 1901-1928, 1940-1942 (Folder 88-203,300-315, 420)
  - Balkan States, 1918-1919 (Folder : 13)
  - Baltic States. (Folder 96)
    See Russia
  - Bamford, Frank S.
    See 10-H
  - Bamman, F.C.
    See 41-H
  - Bananas and banana flour, 1917-1918 (Folder : 14)
  - Barbados. (Folder 96)
  - Barley.
    See Grain; Barley
  - Barnard, Harry E.
    See 6-H; Indiana
  - Barnes, Cecil.
  - Barnes, Julius.
    See Grain Corporation Files, Great Britain, Food Administration, Correspondence
  - Barrington, Lewis.
    See 4-H
  - Bartlett Frazier, reports.
    See 31-H
  - Baruch, Bernard M.
    See War Industries Board
  - Bathurst, Sir Charles (Lord Bledisloe).
    See Great Britain, Food Administration, Correspondence; Great Britain, British War Mission
  - Beale, Sir John Field.
    See Great Britain, Food Administration, Correspondence.
  - Bean investigation.
    See New York; 6-H; 44-H
  - Beans and peas.
    See Soya beans; Vegetables-Beans and peas; 18-H; 21-H
  - Beer and liquor, correspondence, 1917-1918. (Folder 96: 15)
    See also Alcohol; Brewing; Malt
  - Beer and liquor, correspondence, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 97: 1-8)
  - Belgium, 1917-1919. (Folder 97: 9-10)
    See also Commission for Relief in Belgium
  - Bell, C. E., See 31-H
  - Bell, James F., See 48-H; Milling Division File
  - Bentley, C. H., See 18-H
  - Bermuda., See West Indies, British
  - Bernhardt, Joshua., See 17-H; 48-H
  - Bernstein, Irving., See 15-H; 21-H; 30-H
  - Bestor, A. E., See 5-H
  - Beverages, 1917-1919. (Folder 97: 11)
    See also Beer and liquor; Coffee
  - Bevier, Isabel., See 5-H
  - Bibliographies on food and food questions, 1915-1918 (Folder 97: 12-14)
  - Bicarbonate of soda., See Soda ash, etc.
  - Binder twine., See Sisal
  - Bledisloe, Lord (Sir Charles Bathurst)., See Great Britain, Food Administration, Correspondence
  - Blockade and censorship, 1917-1919. (Folder 98: 1-2)
    See also War Trade Board (WTB)
  - Blood albumen, 1918 (Folder 98: 3)
  - Boden, P. B., See 43-H
  - Bolivia, exports and imports, 1918 (Folder 98: 4)
  - Bone black, 1918 (Folder 98: 5)
  - Boret, Victor., See France, Food Administration, Reports 56-57; France, Food Ministry
  - Bowman John M., See 43-H (Folder 98)
  - Boy Scouts of America, 1917-1918 (Folder : 6)
  - Boyden, R. W., See 44-H
  - Brand, Charles J., See Agriculture Department
  - Brandeis, Alfred., See 44-H
  - Brazil, exports and imports, 1917-1918 (Folder 98: 7)
  - Brazil, prices, 1918 (Folder 98: 8)
  - Bread and baking., See 26-H; 33-H; 47-H; Grain-Wheat
  - Bread-returned to bakers, stale, 1917 (Folder 98: 9)
  - Bread subsidy., See 33-H
  - Brewing, 1917-1919. (Folder 98: 10-12)
    See also Beer and liquor; Grain used in brewing
  - British.
    See Great Britain
  - Brooke, Captain.
    See Great Britain, Food Administration, Correspondence
  - Brookings, Robert S.
    See War Industries Board, Price Fixing Committee
  - Brooks, F. S.
  - Brown, E. C.
    See 44-H
  - Brown, Everett S.
  - Brown, H. M.
    See 32-H
  - Buckland, Carl P.
  - Budgets, 1917 (Folder 98: 13)
  - Building Plans.
  - Bulgaria, 1918 (Folder : 14)
  - Bundy, H. H. (Folder 98)
    See 14-H
  - Bunkering.
    See War Trade Board (WTB), Regulations, Bunkering
  - Burch. D. S.
    See 12-H, Farm Journals Section
  - Burden, Henry.
    See 18-H
  - Burlap.
    See Containers; Sisal
  - C correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 98: 15-20)
  - C correspondence, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 99: 1-12)
  - Cacao, circa 1917 (Folder 99: 13)
  - Cafeteria, 1917-1919 (Folder 99: 14)
  - Calcium Carbide, 1918 (Folder 99: 1)
  - Campbell, W. H., See 39-H (Folder 100)
  - Camphor, 1918 (Folder : 2)
  - Camps and cantonments, 1917-1919. (Folder 100: 3)
    See also Waste
  - Canada, 1917-1920. (Folder 100)
    See also 25-H
    - General, 1917-1918 (Folder 100-101: 4)
    - Agriculture, crops, etc., 1918 (Folder 100: 5)
    - Agriculture Department, Production and Thrift (Folder 100: 6)
    - Agricultural War Book, 1916 (Folder 100)
    - Bureau of Statistics, 1917-1920 (Folder : 7-8)
    - Clothing. (Folder 100)
      See American Red Cross
    - Cost of living, 1917-1918 (Folder : 9)
    - Cost of bread production, 1917-1918 (Folder 100: 10-11)
    - Exports and imports, 1916-1919 (Folder 100: 12)
    - Food Board, 1917-1920 (Folder 100)
      - Dairy products, 1918 (Folder 100: 13)
      - Education Division, 1917-1918 (Folder 100: 14)
      - Fruit, vegetables, 1918 (Folder 100: 15)
      - Grain, flour, bread (baking and milling), 1917-1919 (Folder 100: 16-18)
      - Hotels and restaurants, 1918 (Folder 100: 1)
      - Information Division, 1917-1918 (Folder 101: 2)
      - Meat and livestock, 1917-1920 (Folder 101: 3)
      - Prices, 1917 (Folder 101: 4)
      - Rules and regulations, 1917-1918 (Folder 101: 5-11)
      - Sugar, 1917-1918 (Folder 101: 12)
    - Food in storage, 1917-1918 (Folder 101: 13-15)
    - Grain used in alcoholic beverages, 1917 (Folder 101: 16)
  - Canary Islands onions.
    See Vegetables, onions
  - Candy, 1917-1918 (Folder 101: 17)
  - Canned goods, 1917-1919. (Folder 101: 18-20)
    See also Federal Trade Commission (FTC), Food investigation, Report on canned foods, Canned salmon
  - Canning and drying, 1917-1918 (Folder 101: 1)
  - Capper, Arthur, Governor of Kansas, 1917-1918 (Folder 102: 2)
  - Carbide, 1918 (Folder 102: 3)
  - Carry, E. F. (Folder 102)
    See Shipping Board
  - Cartoons, 1917-1920 (Folder 102: 4-7)
  - Cash and carry, 1918 (Folder 102: 8)
  - Casings conference, 1918 (Folder 102: 9)
  - Cassels, S. J. (Folder 102)
    See 38-H
  - Cassova.
    See Food substitutes, Statistical Bulletin 800
  - Castor oil, 1918-1920. (Folder : 10)
    See also Brazil
  - Caustic soda. (Folder 102)
    See Soda ash, etc.; Exports, Potash
  - Censorship.
    See Blockade
  - Central America, 1918. (Folder 102: 11)
    See also Costa Rica; Guatemala; Honduras; Honduras, British; Nicaragua; Panama; World Trade Board Research Bureau, Rationing, Latin America
  - Central Bureau of Planning and Statistics, Weekly Statistical News, no. 12, 27 November 1918 (Folder 102: 12)
  - Chadbourne, W. A.
    See World Trade Board, Foreign agents
  - Chain stores, 1917-1918 (Folder : 13)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the U.S.A., 1917-1921 (Folder 102: 14-16)
  - Chamberlain, A.L.
  - Chambers, Edward.
    See 31-H, Railroad Administration
  - Champ, Frederick P.
  - Charcoal, 1917 (Folder 102: 17)
  - Charts, graphs, and maps, 1917-1918 (Folder 102: 18)
  - Chase, Stephen.
    See 15-H; 17-H
  - Cheese.
    See Dairy products; 34-H; 35-H
  - Chemical Alliance, Committee on Fertilizers, 1918 (Folder 102: 19-21)
  - Chemicals and drugs, 1917-1918. (Folder 102: 22)
    See also Dyes; Exports-Chemicals and Drugs; Fertilizers; 39-H; Germany-Dyes; Iodine Combination
  - Chewing gum.
    See C correspondence
  - Chicago Board of Trade, 1917-1919. (Folder 102: 23)
    See also Grain exchanges
  - Chicory, 1918 (Folder 103: 1)
  - Child, Huntley.
    See Bread and baking; 21-H; 47-H
  - Children, Nutrition of, Policy of Food Administration, 1918 (Folder 103: 2)
  - Childs restaurants, 1918. (Folder 103: 3)
    See also 43-H
  - Chile, nitrate industry, 1918-1919. (Folder 103: 4-5)
    See also Grain, Chile (Flour shipments), Nitrate industry, Iodine Combination
  - China, 1917-1919. (Folder 103: 6-8)
    See also Labor, Chinese, Manchuria
  - Civil Service, 1917. (Folder 103: 9)
    See also 2-H
  - Clarkson, Grosvenor B.
    See Council of National Defense
  - Clothing.
  - Clow, Kent S.
  - Clynes, J. R.
  - Coal, 1917-1919. (Folder 103: 10)
    See also 20-H
  - Coal tar products, 1917-1918 (Folder 103: 11)
  - Cobb, Frank I. (Folder 103)
    See The World, correspondence
  - Cocoa.
    See Beverages
  - Cocoanut (Coconut), 1917 (Folder 103: 12)
  - Coffee, 1917-1919. (Folder 103: 13-16)
    See also 21-H; 44-H
  - Coit, Mary.
    See 27-H
  - Colby, Everett.
    See 45-H
  - Cold Storage.
    See 35-H
  - Collins, James H.
  - Colombia, 1917-1918 (Folder 103: 17)
  - Comfort, Ralph M.
  - Commission Reguladora.
    See 39-H (Merrill)
  - Commerce Department, 1917-1919
    - Correspondence, 1917-1919 (Folder 103: 18-19)
    - Regulations, 1918 (Folder 104: 1)
    - Secretary William C. Redfield, 1917-1919 (Folder 104: 2-3)
    - Safeguard the Gateways of Alaska; Her Waterways, by E. Lester Jones, 1918 (Folder 104: 4)
  - Commission for Relief in Belgium, 1917-1919 (Folder 104: 5)
  - Commission of Inquiry, Report into the Milling Division.
    See Milling Division
  - Commission merchants, 1918 (Folder 104: 6)
  - Commission Permanente Internationale des Contingents.
    See Switzerland
  - Committee on Public Information, 1917-1919 (Folder 104)
    - Correspondence, 1917-1919 (Folder 104: 7-8)
    - Publications, 1917-919 (Folder 104: 9-10)
  - Community centers.
  - Community kitchens, 1918 (Folder 104: 11)
  - Conference of Food Controllers, London.
  - Conger, S. B.
    See Denmark; War Trade Board
  - Congress, 1917-1919 (Folder 104-106)
    - House of Representatives, 1917-1920. (Folder 104-105)
      - Correspondence, 1917-1920 (Folder 104: 12-15)
      - Correspondence, 1917-1920 (contd.) (Folder 105: 1-3)
      - Agricultural Committee, Asbury F. Lever, 1917-1918 (Folder 105: 4-6)
      - Resolutions, Bills, and Acts, 1917-1918 (Folder 105: 8-9)
      - Jouett Shouse, 1917-1918 (Folder 105: 10)
    - Senate, 1917-1919 (Folder 105-106)
      - Correspondence, 1917-1919 (Folder 105: 11-14)
      - Correspondence, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 106: 1-3)
      - Agricultural Committee, 1917 (Folder 106: 4)
      - Bimonthly reports to, on the number of civil employees in the Food Administration, 23 January - 7 July 1919 (Folder 106: 5)
      - Resolutions, Bills, and Acts, 1917-1918 (Folder 106: 6)
      - Morris Sheppard, 1917-1918 (Folder 106: 7)
  - Conscription.
    See Draft Law
  - Conservation of food.
  - Consumer's Council, London.
  - Containers, 1917-1918. (Folder 106: 8-9)
    See also Packages
  - Conversion tables.
    See Weights and measures
  - Cook, N. J.
  - Cooksey, R. C.
    See Treasury Department
  - Cooper, F. E.
  - Coordination of Purchase. (Folder 203)
    See 22-H
  - Copper sulphate, 1917 (Folder : 10)
  - Copra, 1917-1918 (Folder 106: 11)
  - Corn. (Folder 106)
    See Grain, Corn
  - Corn Belt Meat Producers Association, 1918 (Folder : 12)
  - Cosgrove, J. O. A. (Folder 106)
  - Cost of living, 1918. (Folder 106)
    See also Council of National Defense
    - Loaf of bread, 1918 (Folder 106: 13)
    - Pound of bacon, beef, bread, milk, 1918 (Folder 106: 14)
  - Costa Rica, 1917-1918 (Folder 106: 15)
  - Cotton and cottonseed products, 1917-1920. (Folder 106: 16)
    See also 38-H
  - Cotton, J. P.
    See 15-H; Great Britain, Food Administration, Correspondence
  - Council of National Defense, 1917-1921.
    See also War Industries Board
    - Correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder : 17-20)
    - Correspondence, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 106: 1)
    - Minutes of meetings, 1917 (Folder 107: 2)
    - Director Walter S. Gifford, 1917-1918 (Folder 107: 3-4)
    - Secretary Grosvenor B. Clarkson, 1919 (Folder 107: 5)
    - Annual reports, 1917-1918 (Folder 107: 6)
    - Economy in Retail Service, Commercial Economy Board, 1918 (Folder 107: 7)
    - Cooperation in medical instruction, 1917 (Folder 107: 8)
    - Memoranda transmitted to Committee on Appropriations, House of Representatives, 27 December 1919. (Folder 107: 9)
      Includes personal letter of Grosvenor Clarkson to Chairman James W. Good, 1920
    - Minutes of meetings, 1917-1921 (Folder 107: 10-18)
    - Woman's Committee, 1917-1919 (Folder 107: 19)
    - Daily Digest of Reconstruction News, 1919 (Folder 108: 1-2)
    - No Price-Fixing by Advisory Commission of Council of National Defense, by Dr. Hollis Godfrey, Boston Sunday Post, July 27, 1919 (Folder 108: 3)
    - A Preliminary Draft of a Report on Industrial Readjustment in Relations to the High Cost of Living, 1919 (Folder 108: 4-12)
    - Mother Goose in War Time, by the Department of Patriotic Education, 1918 (Folder 108: 13)
  - Country Unite Plan, by F. R. Carpenter, circa 1918 (Folder 108: 14)
  - Cover, John H.
  - Craig, A. U.
    See 12-H, Negro Press
  - Cranston, R. E.
    See 39-H
  - Cravath, Paul.
  - Crespi, Silvio.
    See Italy.
  - Crockett, A. S.
    See 43-H
  - Crop reports, 1917-1918 (Folder 108: 15)
  - Crosby, O. T.
    See Great Britain, Food Administration, Correspondence, Treasury Department
  - Crosby, S. L.
  - Crowder, Maj. Gen. Enoch H.
  - Crowell, Frank G.
    See Grain Corporation File
  - Cryolite cargoes, 1918 (Folder 108: 16)
  - Cuba, 1917-1919 (Folder 108)
    - Correspondence, 1917-1919. (Folder 108-109: 17-19)
      Includes reports
    - Correspondence, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 108: 1-2)
    - Representative in Cuba of the Food & Fuel Administration, Trade & Shipping Boards of the United States, Henry H. Morgan, 1917-1919 (Folder 109: 3-11)
    - Sugar agreement, 1917 (Folder 109: 12)
  - Cullen, George A.
    See 5-H, Cooperating organizations
  - Culver, Wm. B.
    See Federal Trade Commission
  - Czechoslovakia, 1917-1919 (Folder 109: 13)
  - D correspondence, 1917-1919 (Folder 109: 14-15)
  - D correspondence, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 109: 1-6)
  - Dehydration, 1917-1918 (Folder 110)
    - Correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 110: 7-9)
    - Fruits, 1917 (Folder 110: 10)
    - Vegetables, 1917 (Folder 110: 11)
    - Meat, 1917 (Folder 110: 12)
    - Machinery, 1917 (Folder 110: 13)
  - Denmark, 1917-1919 (Folder 110)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1917-1919 (Folder 110: 14)
    - Agreements with U.S., 1917-1918 (Folder 110: 1-2)
    - Agriculture, 1917-1918 (Folder 111: 3)
    - Summary of Conger's Report on Food Situation, 1917 (Folder 111: 4)
    - Economic and political conditions, 1917-1918 (Folder 111: 5-6)
    - Exports and imports, 1917-1918 (Folder 111: 7)
    - Food Administration, 1917-1919 (Folder 111)
      - Reports, 1917-1918 (Folder 111: 8-9)
      - Bread and grains, 1917 (Folder 111: 10)
      - Fats and oils, 1917-1918 (Folder 111: 11)
      - Feeding staff, 1917 (Folder 111: 12)
      - Meat and Livestock, 1917-1918 (Folder 111: 13)
      - Prices, 1918-1919 (Folder 111: 14)
      - Rations, 1918 (Folder 111: 15)
      - Food from Ukraine, 1918 (Folder 111: 16)
      - Imports from U.S., 1917-1919 (Folder 111: 17)
    - Tonnage negotiations, 1918 (Folder 111: 1)
    - Trade with Germany, 1917-1918 (Folder 112: 2-4)
  - Dietary, correspondence, reports, survey, 1917-1918 (Folder 112: 5-8)
  - "A Dietary for Miners," by S.N. Brockunier, Engineering and Mining Journal, 1918 (Folder 112: 9)
  - "Dollar-a-Year-Men,", 1920 (Folder 112: 10)
  - Draft Act, 1917-1918 (Folder 112: 11-15)
  - Dye makers, 1917-1919 (Folder 112: 16)
  - E correspondence, 1917-1919 (Folder 112: 17-18)
  - E correspondence, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 112: 1-2)
  - East Indies, 1917-1918 (Folder 113)
  - British, 1918. (Folder 113: 3)
    See also Pacific Islands
  - Dutch, 1917-1918. (Folder 113: 4)
    See also Netherlands; Pacific Islands
  - Eaton, Wm. D. (Folder 113: 5)
  - Economic cooperation after peace.
    See Germany, Post war trade and reconstruction
  - Ecuador, 1917-1918 (Folder 113: 6)
  - Edgar, William C., 1917-1919 (Folder 113: 7-8)
  - Edwards, J. D.
    See 15-H; 35-H; 42-H
  - Efficiency Bureau, 1918 (Folder 113: 9)
  - Eggs, 1917-1918 (Folder 113: 10)
  - Ekengran, W. A. F.
    See Sweden
  - Eldred, Wilfred, The Wheat and Flour Trade Under Food Administration Control; 1917-1918 (Folder 113: 11)
  - Elliot, Captain F. B.
  - Elliot, Wm.
    See 6-H, South Carolina; 38-H
  - Ellis, T. A.
  - Eltzbacher, Paul.
    See Germany, Food Ministry
  - Employment Service.
    See Labor Department
  - Enemy aliens.
    See Alien enemies
  - Enemy trade.
    See Germany, Exports and imports; War Trade Board, Enemy Trade Bureau.
  - Enforcement Division.
  - Esberg, A. I.
    See 47-H
  - Eustace, H. J.
  - Evans, S. F.
  - Everts, Katherine Jewell.
    See E Correspondence
  - Exemption.
  - Exports, 1908-1920 (Folder 113-118)
    - Africa, 1918 (Folder 113: 12)
    - Ammonia and ammonia sulphate, 1917-1918 (Folder 113: 13)
    - Beer and liquors, 1916 (Folder 113: 14)
    - Beverages, 1918 (Folder 113: 15)
    - Blasting caps, 1917 (Folder 113: 16)
    - Breadstuffs.
      See Exports-Grain
    - Candles and stearin, 1917-1918 (Folder 113: 17)
    - Carbolic acid, 1917-1918 (Folder 113: 18)
    - Caustic potash, 1917-1918 (Folder 113: 19)
    - Caustic soda, 1917-1918 (Folder 113: 20-21)
    - Cereals, circa 1917. (Folder 113: 22)
      See also Exports-Grain
    - Chemicals and drugs, 1917-1918 (Folder 113: 23)
    - Chrome, 1918 (Folder 113: 24)
    - Containers, 1916-1918 (Folder 114: 1)
    - Copper, 1917 (Folder 114: 2)
    - Copra, 1917-1918 (Folder 114: 3)
    - Cotton, 1917-1918 (Folder 114: 4)
    - Cyanide, 1917-1918 (Folder 114: 5-6)
    - Dairy products, 1916-1918 (Folder 114)
      - General, 1917-1918 (Folder 114: 7)
      - Butter, 1917-1918 (Folder 114: 8)
      - Cheese, 1917-1918 (Folder 114: 9)
      - Milk, 1916-1918 (Folder 114: 10)
    - Dyes, 1918 (Folder 114: 11)
    - Explosives, 1918 (Folder 114: 12)
    - Fats and oils, 1911-1919 (Folder 114)
      - General, 1911-1918 (Folder 114: 13)
      - Animal, 1911-1918 (Folder 114: 14-19)
      - Oleomargarine, 1918 (Folder 114: 20)
      - Oleo oil, 1916-1918 (Folder 115: 1)
      - Vegetable, 1916-1919 (Folder 115: 2-6)
    - Feeding stuffs, 1911-1918 (Folder 115)
      - General, 1911-1918 (Folder 115: 7)
      - Hay, 1917-1918 (Folder 115: 8)
      - Mill feed, 1917-1918 (Folder 115: 9)
      - Oil cakes, 1917-1918 (Folder 115: 10)
    - Fertilizers, 1917-1918 (Folder 115: 11)
    - Fish, 1917-1918 (Folder 115: 12-13)
    - Flax and flaxseed, 1917 (Folder 115: 14)
    - Food and feeding stuffs, 1917-1919 (Folder 115: 15-17)
    - Food values, 1917-1918 (Folder 115: 18)
    - Fruits, 1917-1918 (Folder 115: 19)
    - Glucose, 1917-1918 (Folder 115: 20)
    - Glycerin, 1917-1918 (Folder 115: 21)
    - Grain, 1908-1920 (Folder 116)
      - General, 1908-1920 (Folder 116: 1)
      - Barley, 1917-1918 (Folder 116: 2)
      - Corn and cornmeal, 1917-1918 (Folder 116: 3)
      - Oats, 1917-1918 (Folder 116: 4)
      - Rice, 1918 (Folder 116: 5)
      - Rye, 1916-1918 (Folder 116: 6)
      - Wheat and flour, 1916-1920 (Folder 116: 7)
    - Iron and steel, 1918 (Folder 116: 8)
    - Leather, hides, and shoes, 1917 (Folder 116: 9)
    - Livestock, 1913-1918 (Folder 116: 10)
    - Malt, 1918 (Folder 116: 11)
    - Meat, 1912-1918 (Folder 116)
      - General, 1916-1918 (Folder 116: 12)
      - Pork and pork products, 1912-1918 (Folder 116: 13)
      - Beef, 1912-1918 (Folder 116: 14)
      - Mutton, 1911-1918 (Folder 116: 15)
    - Mercury, 1917-1918 (Folder 116: 16)
    - Molasses and syrup, 1918 (Folder 116: 17)
    - Nets, 1917-1918 (Folder 116: 18)
    - Neutrals, 1914-1918 (Folder 116: 19)
    - Paper, 1918 (Folder 116: 20)
    - Peanuts, 1911-1918 (Folder 116: 21)
    - Petroleum, 1918 (Folder 116: 22)
    - Primary and secondary exports, 1914-1915 (Folder 116: 23)
    - Quinine and cinchona bark, 1918-1919 (Folder 117: 1-2)
    - Radium compounds, 1918 (Folder 117: 2)
    - Saccharine, 1918 (Folder 117: 3)
    - Seeds, general, 1917-1919 (Folder 117: 4-5)
    - Seeds, corn, 1917-1919 (Folder 117: 6-9)
    - Soap, 1910-1918 (Folder 117: 10)
    - Soya bean flour, 1918 (Folder 117: 11)
    - Sugar, 1917-1918 (Folder 117: 12-13)
    - Sulphur, 1917 (Folder 117: 14)
    - Superphosphates, 1918 (Folder 117: 15)
    - Tapioca dextrin, 1918 (Folder 117: 16)
    - Vegetables, 1911-1918 (Folder 118)
      - General, 1911-1918 (Folder 118: 1)
      - Beans and peas, 1917-1918 (Folder 118: 2)
      - Onions, 1918 (Folder 118: 3)
      - Potatoes, 1917-1918 (Folder 118: 4)
    - Wood distillates, 1918 (Folder 118: 5)
    - Exports Administrative Board, 1917 (Folder 118: 6)
    - Exports Council, 1917 (Folder 118: 7)
    - Reports, correspondence, and summary, 1911-1918 (Folder 118: 8-11)
  - F correspondence, 1917-1919 (Folder 118: 12-16)
  - F correspondence, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 119: 1-3)
  - Fair Prices.
    See Prices, "Fair price"
  - Fairs, 1918 (Folder 119: 4)
  - Farm labor.
    See Labor
  - Farm machinery, 1917. (Folder 119: 5)
    See also Agricultural Implements
  - Farmer's unions, 1918 (Folder 119: 6)
  - Fats and oils.
    See 38-H; 42-H
  - Fats, oils and oilseeds.
    See Flax, Flaxseeds and linseeds; Peanuts and peanut products
  - Federal Reserve Bank, 1917 (Folder 119: 7)
  - Federal Reserve Board, 1917-1918 (Folder 119: 8)
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1917-1926
    - William B. Colver, Chairman, 1917-1918 (Folder 119: 9-10)
    - Reports, 1917-1926 (Folder 119)
      - Flour Milling and Flour Jobbing, 1918 (Folder 119: 11)
      - Meat-Packing Industry, 1919 (Folder 119: 12)
      - Bakery Section, 1917 (Folder 119: 13)
      - Grain Trade, 1920-1926 (Folder 119: 14-15)
      - Grain Trade, 1920-1926 (contd.) (Folder 120: 1-2)
      - Commercial Wheat Flour Milling, 1920 (Folder 120: 3)
      - Profiteering, 1918 (Folder 120: 4)
      - Annual for the fiscal year ending June 30, 1919 (Folder 120: 5)
    - Correspondence, 1917-1919 (Folder 120: 6-7)
  - Feeding stuffs, 1917-1919 (Folder 120)
    - General, 1917-1919 (Folder 120: 8-11)
    - General, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 121: 1)
    - Brewer's grains, 1917 (Folder 121: 2)
    - Brewer's yeast, 1917. (Folder 121: 3)
      See also Yeast
  - Fer-Flo.
    See box 128-129
  - Food, 1917-1919. (Folder 121)
    See also Diet; 11-H; Advisory Committee on Alimentation; Food situation
    - Food and Home Service League, 1917 (Folder 121: 4)
    - Notes, 1918 (Folder 121: 5)
    - Parcels for American soldiers, 1918 (Folder 121: 6)
    - Preservation, 1917 (Folder 121: 7)
    - Sales channels, circa 1917 (Folder 121: 8)
    - Foreign situation, 1917-1919 (Folder 121: 9)
    - Substitutes, 1917-1918 (Folder 121: 10)
    - Values, 1917-1918 (Folder 121: 11-13)
  - Forbes, 1917 (Folder 121: 14)
  - Formulas of food offered for conservation, 1917 (Folder 121: 15)
  - France, 1914-1919 (Folder 121)
    - General, 1917-1918 (Folder 121: 16)
    - American Embassy, Paris, 1917-1918 (Folder 121: 17)
    - Agreement with Spain, 1918 (Folder 121: 18)
    - Finance, 1918 (Folder 121: 19)
    - Exports and imports, 1917-1918 (Folder 121: 20)
    - USFA, 1917-1919 (Folder 121-124)
      - Correspondence, 1917-1919 (Folder 121)
        - A-Z (Folder 121: 21-23)
        - A-Z (contd.) (Folder 122: 1-5)
        - Durand, Dana (Folder 122: 6)
        - Kellogg, Vernon L., See also box 140 (Folder 122: 7)
        - Mitchell, Sydney A. (Folder 122: 8-10)
        - Simpson, John (Folder 122: 11-15)
      - Accounts, 1918 (Folder 122: 16)
      - Reports, 1917-1918 (Folder 122-124)
        - Algeria, 1918 (Folder 122: 17)
        - Agricultural, 1918 (Folder 122: 18)
        - Consumption of pork and milk, 1918 (Folder 122: 19)
        - Crops and cereal situation, 1917-1918 (Folder 123: 1-3)
        - Laws, orders, and directions, 1917 (Folder 123: 4)
        - Provisioning service, 1917 (Folder 123: 5)
        - French Rationing System, 1918 (Folder 123: 6)
        - Prices, 1918 (Folder 123: 7)
        - Food conditions in various sections of France, 1917-1918 (Folder 123: 8-11)
        - French Food Imports, 1918 (Folder 123: 12)
        - Letters covering reports, 1917 (Folder 123: 13)
        - Meat and Livestock situation, 1917 (Folder 123: 14)
        - Press reviews from French journals, 1918 (Folder 123: 15)
        - Prices and wages, 1917-1918 (Folder 123: 16)
        - Stocks, 1918 (Folder 123: 17)
        - Great Britain, 1918 (Folder 124: 1)
        - Sugar and saccharine, 1918 (Folder 124: 2-3)